Mahyar Hoseinzadeh

Phone: +98 (912) 6450328

Skype ID: mahyar.hosseinzade

Email: h.mahyar@gmail.com

Birth Date: 1985 Nationality: Iranian

I am SAP Analyst / Consultant with 6+ Years of experience in SAP ERP including 8 full life-cycle implementations, upgrade and support.

Involved in various stages of implementation from Business Blueprint, Gap Analysis, Testing, Cut over planning, Go-Live, Post-live Production Support and End-User Documentation and Training.

Experience in defining project scope, gap analysis, configuration, testing and deployment.

Areas of implementation include industry sectors from FMCG.

SD: Run all processes of Sales orders and Returns processes, FOC, Rebate Processing, ATP Check and Rescheduling, Delivery and Returns Delivery processes, Pricing, Credit Management, Billing, Output Control, Inter-Company Billing for Cross Company Sales, Cross Company STO, Third party sales, and ...

QM: Expertise in Configuration of QM in procurement, production, Sales & distribution, controlling. Excellent Skills in configuring and Customizing Quality Planning (Basic data for Quality Management, Inspection planning), Quality Assurance (Quality inspection, Quality certificates) & Quality Control (Quality notifications, QM information system) in QM module.

LE and WM: Expertise in Configuration of Warehouse Management architecture - Warehouse structure in WM system, Basic stock management, Warehouse Movements, Put away and Picking Strategies, Storage Unit Management. Physical Inventory, Delivery processing in WM, Configuration of WM and IM movement types and linking IM movement's types with WM movement types via reference movement types, Stock Transfers, Posting Changes, Physical Inventory for Warehouse Management.

Work_Experiences

SAP WM, SD, LE and QM consultant at Solico¹ Group Company

March - June 2019	SD and QM and LE consultant in Aris Company Aris is a company of Solico Group that produce different group of Ice Cream in Iran. I worked as a SAP Logistics consultant in two module of SAP ECC implementation projects.
Nov 2018- feb2019	Project manager and SD and QM consultant in Baharan Gol Company Baharan Gol produce different group of chocolate and cream in Iran. I worked as a project manager and also SAP consultant in implementation projects.
June and July 2018	DSD business analyst in Bonny chow Company Bonny chow is a distributor of product of Solico groups that have more than 30 different office in whole of Iran. I worked as a SAP DSD business analyst in SAP ECC implementation projects.
Feb 2018	SD and QM consultant in Kalleh Kermanshah Company As a sub-company of Solico Group that produce 6 different SKU of milk and Iron. I worked as a SAP Logistics consultant in two modules of SAP ECC implementation projects.
Dec 2017-Jan 2018	SD consultant in Kaach Company Kaach company produce different chemical product like as packaging material. I worked as a SAP Logistics consultant in SAP ECC implementation projects.
May 2017	SD consultant in Baghdad distribution Center Solico Bagdad is one of distribution center of Solico group in outside of Iran in Iraq. I worked as a SAP Logistics consultant in SAP ECC implementation projects.
Dec 2016-feb2017	SD and WM consultant in Kalleh Tehran Company Kalleh Tehran is one of the Solico group company that produce different group of Milk and beverage in Iran. I worked as a SAP Logistics consultant in two module of SAP ECC implementation projects.

¹ Biggest beverage and dairy company of Iran

Jan 2014- Sep 2015	SD, WM and LE consultant in Kalleh Amol Company As a main-company of Solico Group, Kalleh Amol produce different group of dairy in Iran. I worked as a SAP Logistics consultant in two module of SAP ECC implementation projects.
July 2012-sep 2013	Manager of Technical & Spare parts warehouse in Kalleh1 dairy
	Inventory of Equipment and Machinery of Solico group
	Head of Crane department in kalleh dairy Company
	Leading of warehouse staff. Engagement to build motivated teams focused on targets achievement.
	Work and manage more than 20 staff
July 2010- July 2012	Boss of body warehouse of Saipa Kashan2 company
	SAIPA-Kashan Automobile Manufacturing Company, a member of SAIPA Group, is the
	largest plant in Middle East was inaugurated in 2010 in Kashan, Isfahan. Extended across
	318 acres, SAIPA-Kashan is one of the biggest car making complexes in Iran. SAIPA-
	Kashan has the potential of producing over 150000 vehicles annually.
	Boss of the Chemical warehouse
	Work and manage more than 50 staff
	Expert of production scheduling and materials supply chain
	Expert of QA documentation and editing documents
	Member of External Kanban implementation team in Saipa group
	Member of Internal Kanban implementation team in Saipa Kashan
	Member of implementation team for IRISA (ERP) Integrated system for warehouse and
	feeding line in Saipa Kashan
	Member of supplier park implementation team Member of Feasibility study And technical review for connection Saipa Kashan to the rail
	network of Iran

 $^{^{\}rm 1}$ Biggest dairy company of Iran $^{\rm 2}$ A branch of the biggest company of car manufacturing in Middle East

Educations

M. Sc in System management productivity

Industrial Engineering Department, University of Tarbiat Modares¹, Tehran, Iran, 2011-2012

B.Sc. in Transportation of Railway

Rail way Engineering Department, Iran University of Science and Technology (IUST)², Tehran, Iran, 2004 – 2009

High school diploma in Mathematics and Physics

 $\textbf{National Organization for Development of Exceptional Talents (NODET)} 3 \;, \; \mathsf{Amol}, \; \mathsf{Iran}, \\$

1999 - 2003

GPA: 18.73/20

Thesis Title

- M.Sc.
 - Improve the process of sending materials from the warehouse to production lines by using Make span definitions.
- B.Sc.
 - MAKER: A New Algorithm in Finding Frequent Item sets
 - It's a new algorithm under the supervision of DR, M. Yaghini⁴, for finding frequent Item sets Based on prime numbers.

Publications

- " A New Algorithm in Finding Frequent Item sets "International Conference on Data Mining (DMIN'11: July 2011, USA)
- Generating Rules to Increase Production Using Decision Tree(DMIN'12 Conference, July 2012,USA)
- Prioritization of organizational learning By Using statistical techniques in Kashan Saipa,(1Th
 Seminar on the role of organizational learning in national production And supporting the
 Iranian capital and labor, Iran Tehran, Fall 2012)
- Rule-Based Production Planning and Scheduling using Decision Tree Interactive Session Information- Annual Meeting, (Annual Meeting, Phoenix –USA, 2012)
- The most important logistic factors affecting the quality of the input items to the Saipa Kashan company by using decision tree technique and the design of experiments(First International Conference on Quality Engineering, Iran - Tehran, Fall 2012)
- Increasing efficiency in the supply chain Dairy industry by using GPS & Data Logger(5th National Conference and the 3rd International Conference on Logistics and Supply Chain, Iran
 Tehran ,Fall 2012)

³ http://www.nodet.net/

¹ http://www.modares.ac.ir/en

² http://www.iust.ac.ir/

⁴ http://webpages.iust.ac.ir/yaghini/

- Generating Rules to Increase Production Using Decision Tree in Car Industry, International PARTICIPATION XIV. BIOSTATIST NATIONAL CONGRESS (Turkey, KAYSERİ, SEPTEMBER2012)
- Reliability of trains arriving at destination, (Third International Conference on Recent Advances in Railway Engineering ICRARE2013-, Iran - Tehran, spring 2013)
- Determining factors in the failure of the signaling system by Using decision trees and regression techniques, (Third International Conference on Recent Advances in Railway Engineering ICRARE2013-, Iran - Tehran, spring 2013)
- Feasibility of a national rail network linking Saipa Kashan, (Third International Conference on Recent Advances in Railway Engineering ICRARE2013, Iran - Tehran, spring 2013)

Computer Skills

Programming Language: C/C++, Pascal, VB

Engineering: AutoCAD, Arena, Spss clementine

Mathematics: Minitab,

CMS WordPress, Joomla...

Others: MS Office Package, Photoshop ,ERP SAP

Language

- Persian(First language)
- English(Fluent)
- Spanish, Arabic (basic)